Ah, hmm.
(Penny:)Oh, God, no, I can't.
Look, Sheldon, honey, I don't want things
to be weird between us.
(Sheldon:)Won't it also be weird if I have to say
hello to you on my way to work...
(Sheldon:)...and you're living in a refrigerator box
and washing your hair with rain water?
(Penny:)I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
(Sheldon:)Of course you will.
(Sheldon:)It's impossible to pay me back
sooner than you can.
Assuming you've subscribed to a linear
understanding of time and causality.
(Penny:)I'm regretting this already.
(Sheldon:)You know,
I've given the matter some thought...
(Sheldon:)...and I think I'd be willing to be a house
pet to a race of super-intelligent aliens.
(Leonard:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)Ask me why.
(Leonard:)Do I have to?
(Sheldon:)Of course. That's how you move
a conversation forward.